

# **ELBA HELEN GEORGE**

#### Software Engineer

Aspiring web developer with a solid foundation in programming, a passion for developing web applications, and a dedication to continuous learning. Backed by 10+ years of teaching experience, offering exceptional problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and a collaborative mindset to the tech domain.

#### **Contact**

+9633010700

elbaheleng@gmail.com

Piravom, Ernakulam

https://github.com/elbaheleng

### Skills



Python SQL Git

Communication Team work

Problem solving Attention to detail

Organisational Skills

#### Languages

English Malayalam Hindi

### **Experience**

Systems Engineer Trainee Jun 2011 - Sept 2011

Infosys Ltd., Mysore

Attended training for 3 months at Mysore on C, SQL and Java.

Assistant Professor
Jan 2012 - Jun 2012

Department of Civil Engineering

Al-Azhar College of Engineering & Technology, Thodupuzha

Assistant Professor Jun 2014 - till date

Department of Civil Engineering

Toc H Institute of Science & Technology, Arakkunnam

#### Certification

Learning Python

Infosys Springboard - November 2024

## **Projects**

Rhythm of life

Online Piano

https://rhythm-of-life.vercel.app

Developed a 13-key interactive piano using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with audio integration.

### **Education**

**B.Tech** Civil Engineering 2007-2011

Toc H Institute of Science & Technology

M.Tech Geomechanics & Structures 2012-2014
 Saintgits College of Engineering